long time no see.
久しぶり
fine?
元気?
I'm really fine.
めっちゃ元気です
What good thing happened recently?
最近あった良いことは?
Has it been a month?
1ヶ月ぶりか?
What good thing happened in the past month?
この1ヶ月であった良いことは?
What's good?
良いことは?
Eh, I wonder what it is.
えー、なんだろう
Oh, but the air conditioner in my house is new.
あ、でも、お家のエアコンが新しくなりました
Wow.
ほー
copper?
どう?
comfortable?
快適?
It's really cool.
めっちゃ涼しい
What do you mean it's broken?
故障したってことは?
No, somehow, all of a sudden, I remembered everything until the day before.
いや、なんか、いきなり、前の日まで覚えてたんだけど、
All of a sudden, the power stopped coming on.
いきなりなんか電源つかなくなっちゃって
Hey.
へー
I thought it was great so I bought it.
やばいって思って買えました
I think it would be quite painful if it broke down at this time of year.
なんかその、この時期に故障するとだいぶ痛いと思うんやけど、
it hurts.
痛い
Does that mean you can go the same day?
即日いけたってことは?
No, for about two weeks.
いや、2週間くらいまで
Wow.
うわー
tight.
きつい
It was crazy.
やばかったです
It's tough.
きついなー
So, in that broken living room,
だから、あの壊れたのリビングで、
But I turned on all the air conditioners in the rooms other than the living room,
でもリビング以外の部屋のエアコン全部つけて、
Open the door fully.
ドアを全開にして
Either that or that.
それか、それか
Ah, that's still good.
あ、それならまだ良いね
I did my best.
頑張りました
Hmm.
う ーん
For example, if you do it with 1K people, oh,
例えば1Kの人とかやったらさ、 ああ、
Is that the case with L?
Lでもそうか
Yeah.
うん
Because there's only one.
1個しかないから
Yeah yeah.
うん うん
It would be tough if it broke.
それ壊れちゃうとね、 きついよね
Apparently there are a lot of them this time of year.
この時期ね、多いらしいからね
You said it was a lot, kind of.
多いって言ってました、なんか
For some reason, it breaks just when it's needed.
必要な時期に何故かね、壊れるという
I'm glad it didn't go away.
無くならなくてよかった
surely.
確かに
There are a lot of heat strokes this year too.
熱中症多いもんね、今年も
Good thing.
良いこと
That's good.
良いことです
Are you working hard on making sweets?
からずお菓子作り頑張ってます?
I'm doing my best.
頑張ってます
I kneaded bread this morning too.
今日も朝パンこねました
That's great, if you have time.
すごいね、暇さえあれば
I've been kneading it.
こねてきました
Do you eat properly?
食べるんちゃんと?
I don't eat.
食べない
Aren't you going to eat it?
食べないの?
I took a bite and thought it was delicious.
一口食べて、美味しいなと思って、
But I'll give it to someone.
でも誰かにあげちゃう
Taste is important.
味見は大事よね
So do you like making things?
じゃあ作るのが好きなの?
that's right.
そうです
I like kneading time.
こねる時間が好きです
I've never kneaded bread, so I don't know.
パンこねたことないからわからないけど
But I'm really attached to it.
でもめっちゃ愛着がきます
Or make it into the shape you like?
自分の好きな形にしたりとか?
I like it, even though it has a lot of femininity.
いいね、女子力高いのにね
As expected.
やっぱ
Well then, let me show you some feminine power.
じゃあちょっと女子力見せてもらおうかな
I don't like it, I thought I'd show it to you.
嫌だな、見せてもらおうかなって
I love this too.
これも大好きな
Take food in the back.
食べ物を後ろでテイクに
It's embarrassing.
恥ずかしい
Have you eaten?
食べてきた?
Today is...
今日は...
Roll...
巻き...
Convenience store stuff that looks like green onion toro rolls.
ネギとろ巻きみたいなコンビニのやつ
The soles of my feet are really squishy.
めっちゃ足裏ぷにぷにやねん
Soft and unusual.
柔らかい、珍しい
Is that a good thing?
いいことなんですか?
Women often wear heels,
結構なんか、女の人ってヒールとかも履くし、
They say it's crunchy, but it's rough.
カリカリって言ってあるけど、ガサガサ
This guy...
こいつ...
Ah, peeling?
あ、ピーリング?
That's right.
そうね
It's meaningful.
意味あるんや
It becomes crispy.
ぱりぱりになる
Poroporoka?
ぽろぽろか
Something
なんか
...
Let's try it.
やって みよう
There are some that are sold at places like Donki.
なんかドンキとかに売ってるやつあるね
Oh, I'm selling it, I'm selling it.
あ、売ってます、売ってます
Something like baby feet
なんかベビーフットの
Guy.
や つ
Well, I decided to have my gums peeled.
なんかあれ、歯茎のピーリングをしたことに
gum?
歯茎?
Yeah.
うん
What is that?
なにそれ?
It's going to be really beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗になる
Gums?
歯茎の?
Yeah.
うん
Will it change?
変化になる?
oh yeah.
そうそう
Hey, it's my first time hearing that.
へー、初めて聞いた
It hurts though.
痛いけどね
It stings.
しみる
no.
いや
It's not a severe pain though.
その、激痛じゃないけど
Yeah.
うん
Because it's really peeling off.
めっちゃ皮めくれてるから
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Teeth blowing?
歯吹きか
It hurts.
痛いな
Well, it'll take a few days.
まあ、2、3日やけどね
Does it hurt?
痛いなんですか?
Yeah yeah.
うんうん
Tingling.
ピリピリ
It hurts when I eat something sour.
酸味あるものとか食べたら、痛い
Ah, yes
あ、そう
What?
なん ですか?
But I've lost a little weight recently.
でも、最近ちょっと痩せたんですよね
Yeah, I lost some weight.
うん、なんか痩せた
Oh, really?
あ、本当ですか?
Neck holder.
首入れが
I lost about 2 kg.
なんか2キロぐらい落ちました
Yeah.
うん
I was able to put my neck in.
首入れできてた
that's right.
そうです
I lost a little weight.
ちょっと痩せました
Lose your breasts.
おっぱい痩して
yes.
はい
Thank you.
ありがとうって
My breasts have also become softer.
おっぱいも柔らかくなった
Is it true?
本当ですか?
a little bit.
ちょっと
Yeah, this is it.
うん、ここが
From before.
前 より
happy.
嬉しい
But I'm a little overweight, so I want to lose more weight.
でも、ちょっと太ってるから、もっと痩せたい
Did you take a shower this morning?
今日は朝シャワー浴びた?
I haven't come in this morning.
今日は、朝入ってない
So, from last night.
じゃあ、昨日の夜から
Last night.
昨日の夜
Are you sweating?
汗が溜まってる?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Let's lick it.
舐めてみよう
dirty.
汚い
Let's lick it.
舐めてみよう
Looks salty.
しょっぱそう
It's just hot, so let's replenish the salt.
ちょうど暑いから塩分補給しよう
TRUE?
本当?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
hard.
辛い
amazing.
すごい
Oh, I don't like it.
え、嫌だ
Well, I hate it, but I'm not taking a shower.
え、嫌なんだけど、シャワー入ってないよ
Oh, I don't like it.
え、嫌だ
Dirty?
汚れた?
Did you see there?
あそこ見た?
I don't like it.
嫌だ
I don't like it, I don't like it.
嫌だ、嫌だ
Don't you like it?
嫌だ?
I don't like it.
嫌だよ
So, can I have a chew?
じゃあ、チューしてくれていいですか?
TRUE?
本当?
face,
顔、
face.
顔
Your face looks great.
顔、 めっちゃ映ってる
Do you sweat in the shower?
シャワーで汗流す?
Maki, you don't have to wash it too much.
マキ、あまり洗わなくていいよ
I'll lick it.
俺、舐めるから
I don't like it.
嫌だ
Don't add salt again.
また塩分補給するな
But it's all about salt, and when I have enough, I sweat a lot,
でも、やっぱ塩分ね、足りてる時って汗しょっぱいんだけど、
When I don't have enough, my sweat doesn't feel salty at all.
足りてない時、汗、全然しょっぱくないんだよ
Ah, that's right.
あ、そうなんだよ
That's how I understand.
それで分かる
I feel like I don't have enough salt.
塩、足りてないな、みたいな
The same goes for Sportsline.
スポーツラインとかもこうですよ
sodium.
ナトリウム
battery.
バッテリー
Then wash me too.
じゃあ、俺も洗って
Shower cleaning.
シャワー洗浄
Chin Chin, now it's beautiful.
チンチン、綺麗になったわ
So beautiful.
めっちゃ綺麗
Wash your mouth.
お口洗浄
Does it tickle when you touch it?
ひたって触られたらくすぐったい?
Hmm.
うーん
What does it feel like?
なんの感じだ?
Tie it up.
よりめして
Yorime?
よりめ?
Yeah.
うん
How do I do it?
どうやってやる?
cute.
かわいい
Well then, while you're twisting, don't put your neck on that side.
じゃあ、よりめしながら、あっち首ダメよ
Yorime?
よりめ?
Yes, that's right.
そう、よりめはそう
What should I do if it goes away?
しまったら、どうしよう
Yorime is right away.
よりめは、すぐで
Oh, lie?
あ、嘘?
I'll laugh, just like that.
笑っちゃうよ、そのまま
First, let's check your liver.
まず、肝臓チェックしよう
bean paste
あん
Mari?
まり?
No, it's the worst.
いや、 最悪
Why are you Kagun?
なんで、かぐんですか?
I can smell it.
チンチンって、かぐんだよ
No, it's Hakamano.
ちがう、はかまので
Then it won't get rough.
そったら、荒れないでも
It gets really rough.
めっちゃ、荒れる
Hey.
ねえ
Does it sting?
ひりひりする?
It doesn't sting, but it's kind of...
ひりひりはしないけど、 なんかね、
I get itchy.
かゆくなっちゃう
lol
笑
I woke up because I was going on a trip tomorrow.
明 日から旅に出るから、目を覚めた
Do you play like that at home too?
家でも、そうやって遊んでるの?
No, I don't play.
いや、遊ばない
I'm being kind now.
優しくしてる、今
Can I lick the embarrassing part?
恥ずかしいとこ、舐めていい?
I want to lick it.
舐めたい
Doesn't it feel good?
気持ちいいとかはない?
It feels like a tickling feeling.
くすぐった気持ちみたい
Yeah, it's really ticklish.
うん、めっちゃくすぐったい
I feel really nervous.
なんか、すごい、そわそわする
It's ticklish, too.
くすぐったい、こっちも
You can lick this too.
こ っちも舐めていいじゃん
You said it was ticklish.
くすぐったかったり、言ってたじゃん
My butt and here are ticklish.
お尻とこっち、くすぐったい
My butt is more ticklish.
お尻のほうが、くすぐったい
How was your finger?
指はどうでした?
Well then, next time I'll let you lick me.
じゃあ、次、俺の舐めてもらおうかな
Okay.
よ いしょ
Excuse me.
失礼します
I'll enjoy having this.
いただきます
I'll have it.
いただきますよ
I'm playing.
遊んでるやん
I'm not playing.
遊んでないよ
It's really tight.
すごくしばりやねん
Is it worth it?
わりしてる?
Can I get you something?
何 か出していい?
Please take it out.
出してくださいよ
出してください
Please send it to something.
何かに出してくださいよ
Please take it out.
出してください
Do you like it at first?
最初、好き?
It never comes out.
いつまでも出てこない
You've lost weight.
痩せたね
I lost weight.
痩せた
No, like this.
違う、こう
why?
なんで?
I like your face.
顔とかがいい
Because it looks quick.
パッと見えるからね
That's right.
そうなんだ
I feel like my stomach drops the most, first.
一番お腹が落ちる気がする、最初に
It depends on the person.
人によるけどな
I'm not hungry.
俺はお腹落ちない
My face falls.
顔落ちる
The easiest to fall off.
一番落ちやすい
I can see by looking at my stomach that I have lost weight.
お腹見てわかる、痩せたなって
I've started to lose weight, starting from my face and stomach.
顔から、腹からするから、痩せ始めたな、
Like.
みたいな
My legs started shaking again.
また足プルプル始まった
Leg pull time has arrived.
足プルタイムきた
It starts again.
また始まる
I think maybe the state I'm in is dangerous.
た ぶん、この立ててる状態が、やばいんだと思う
this is?
これは?
Maybe this is okay.
たぶん、これは平気
It starts when you use your inner muscles.
内側筋肉使ってると始まる
But maybe that's not the case.
でも、そんなことないのかも
Jiggly time.
プルプルタイム
The inside is amazing every time.
毎回、内側がすごい
Isn't it just the left side?
左だけじゃない?
But I also do the right one sometimes.
でも、右もたまにする
How many eyes do you have?
プルプル何個の目?
No jiggle?
プルプル無し?
Try to suck it hard
強く吸ってみ
hand.
て
Is it difficult?
や りにくい?
Your posture is important.
体勢大事や
Why don't you talk like that?
なんで、そんなもん喋らんの?
I'm tired.
疲れちゃった